(Dr Lorvis:)Welcome to
my Fortress of Solitude.
(Dr Lorvis:)This is where I go
to get away from...
(Dr Lorvis:)all my other solitude.
(Howard:)Oh, come on.
It's a replica.
(Man:)Original.
(Howard:)Oh, I think I just
cheated on my wife.
The gun from Hellboy?
(Dr Lorvis:)Yup.
(Raj:)How did you get it?
(Dr Lorvis:)Bought it at auction.
(Raj:)Oh, I was hoping
for a juicy tidbit
(Raj:)about Ron Perlman's testicles.
WOMAN:
Oliver! I'm going to play bingo!
(Dr Lorvis:)Okay, Mother. Have fun.
Still lives with his mom.
(Howard:)Yikes, right?
(laughs)
(Raj:)Yeah, I'm not quite
sure how to respond.
Wow, Donkey Kong!
This-this was my game
when I was a kid!
(Sheldon:)Because it's a story
(Sheldon:)of a pretty blonde girl
(Sheldon:)tirelessly pursued
by a small, oddly-shaped man?
(Leonard:)No, because I liked it.